pureromance.com 2012-10-28

# Pure Romance - Privacy & Security

#### Privacy Statement

Pure Romance, LLC or one of its affiliates (collectively, "Pure Romance") operates this Pureromance.com Web site (the "Site"). Pure Romance respects the privacy of visitors to the Site. We provide this explanation about our online information practices, our "Privacy Policy," to demonstrate our commitment to protect your privacy. We reserve the right to update the Privacy Policy at any time, without notice. We encourage you to visit this page periodically and review the then current terms. Pure Romance collects client information to enhance your shopping experience. This privacy policy is intended to assist you in understanding what information we gather about you when you visit this Site, how we use that information, and the safeguards we have in place for that information. Pure Romance is a licensee of U.S. Patent No. 6,594,641 which is owned by Reshare Commerce LLC.

This online privacy statement applies to this Site. Pure Romance Consultants may also operate their own Web sites. Each Consultant is an independent contractor having the right to operate their own Pure Romance business, and each is responsible for the privacy and information security policies and practices of those sites. In this regard, a Consultant's online privacy policies and practices may vary from those that apply to this Site. Pure Romance is not responsible for the policies and practices of Pure Romance Consultants in the operation of their independent Web sites.

This Privacy Policy discloses the current privacy practices of Pure Romance and by using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy and consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner described.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact us at 866-ROMANCE.

#### Information We Collect

##### General Browsing Information

Pureromance.com gathers navigational information during each visitor's use of our Site. In the process of gathering navigational information, non-personally identifiable information (e.g., domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address and the like) may be collected. The navigational information tells Pureromance.com about the use of our Site by visitors, including the areas of our site that are most visited or the time of a last visit to a page on our Site. It also tells us about the technical efficiencies of our Site and services (e.g., the time it takes a visitor to connect to our Site or download pages). The navigational information helps us better understand a visitor's experience at Pureromance.com and improve upon that experience by recognizing and delivering more of the features, services and products our visitors prefer. We may provide this statistical information to third parties, but when we do so we do not provide personally identifying information without your permission.

##### Personal Information

Pureromance.com may ask you to provide personal information when you establish or update a Pureromance.com account, sign up for Pure Romance E-mail, enter a contest, participate in a survey, shop online, check the status of an order, request a catalog, purchase and send an e-gift card or create or send a wish list or gift reminder.

Categories of information collected include name, address, e-mail address, recipient's name and e-mail address, order information, telephone number, credit card information and messages or reminders you create.

Pure Romance may collect and store personally identifiable information, to respond to questions, and to process or fill orders or requests. Pure Romance may use this information to provide goods and services that you request and to let you know of additional goods and services about which you might be interested. Pure Romance may also use this information to customize your experience using our Web site.

Pure Romance may also retain transaction and experience information, such as information about your transactions with us, as well as information about our communications with you. Examples include your account history, requests for information and our responses. We may match user information we collect with offline data available from other sources in order to carry out our business and to provide our goods and services and to conduct advertising and promotions more effectively.

For product or service orders, Pure Romance may need additional information in order to process or to fulfill your order or request. Except as otherwise stated in this Policy, Pure Romance will not share your personal information with third parties without your permission, except as otherwise necessary to (i) process or fulfill your order, (ii) respond to your request or answer your inquiries, (iii) forward your information to one or more Pure Romance Consultants so that they may contact you in response to your communications to us; or (iv) comply with any applicable law, court order or other judicial process.

#### Using Personal Information That We Collect

Pure Romance uses the personal information we collect from you to deliver products that you have ordered, to fulfill requests that you have created, to contact you or the product recipient(s) in the event of order or delivery difficulties, for verification purposes, to respond to your inquiries, and to deliver services and information about our products or Web site, including adding you to our print catalogue mailing list.

We will use the information you provide when you visit us to sign up for Pure Romance E-mail to send you updates about Pure Romance products, promotions and events. In addition, we will use your name and mailing address provided during such sign up, in all the ways described in this privacy statement and we will use your e-mail address as described in this privacy statement for e-mail addresses collected after August 25, 2006. In the event you would no longer wish to receive such communications from Pure Romance, please notify us by email at [customerservice@pureromance.com](mailto:customerservice@pureromance.com).

Information you provide to us will be transmitted to and stored in information technology facilities and databases maintained in the United States of America. By submitting information to us, including non-public personal information, you consent to the transmission of your information to and the storage of that information in the United States.

Pure Romance will not sell or rent personally-identifying information collected during your use of our Site without your permission. Pure Romance may, however, transfer your information in the event that we transfer ownership of all or a significant part of our stock, assets or business.

If you place a request for products or services, Pure Romance may use information you provide to us to ship your order.

Pure Romance may rely upon third parties for important elements of our operations, so we may provide your nonpublic personal information, such as your name, address, and account information to these third parties so that they can do their job, such as servicers, financial service providers, marketing companies that help us market our products. We will take appropriate steps to protect your information in these circumstances. These third parties also may have their own privacy policies.

Pure Romance may also share the information we collect about you with third parties including retailers, credit card issuers and processors, banks and other financial institutions and government agencies.

Pure Romance may use your personally-identifying information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout, and services.

Pure Romance may use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests.  We may ask you to provide us voluntarily with additional information regarding your personal or business interests, experience or requests, which we may use to customize our service for you.

Pure Romance may use your e-mail address, your mailing address, and phone number to contact you regarding administrative notices, new product offerings and communications relevant to your use of the Site. If you do not wish to receive these communications, please contact us at [customerservice@pureromance.com](mailto:customerservice@pureromance.com).

Pure Romance may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our Terms of Use or purchase agreements. At times, we may review the status or activity of multiple users to do so. We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our products and services.

Pure Romance may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to manage our Site and to enhance our Site based on the usage pattern data we receive. Pure Romance reserves the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of business or assets to a third party.

#### Cookies

Pureromance.com uses a browser feature known as a cookie. A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer. Cookies are used to help track your clicks and pass information as you go through the pages within Pureromance.com. This allows Pureromance.com to make our Site more responsive to your needs by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. Pureromance.com also uses cookies to keep track of how many items you put into your shopping bag and to remember you when you return to Pureromance.com.  Preference and options configurations in your browser determine if and how a cookie will be accepted. You can change those configurations on your computer if you desire. Please consult your specific browser instructions to learn more about these features. By changing your preferences, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is set, or you can reject all cookies. If you do so and cookies are disabled, you may be required to reenter your information more often and certain features of our site may be unavailable.

#### Privacy Of Children On Our Website

To ensure compliance with federal law, Pureromance.com does not knowingly collect or maintain information provided by children under the age of 18. If a child has provided us with personally-identifying information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information.

#### Links To Other Websites & Services

For your convenience, our Site may contain links to other sites, especially sites operated by independent Pure Romance Consultants. Pure Romance is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to review the separate privacy policies of each site you visit.

#### Updates To Privacy Statement

Please review the Privacy Statement for any material changes made within the last thirty days with respect to categories of information collected at Pureromance.com or material changes in how we use information collected at Pureromance.com (whether a deletion or addition). If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, please visit our site often for this and other important announcements about Pureromance.com.

#### Consent

Pure Romance respects the online privacy of all visitors to our website. By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Pure Romance in a manner consistent with the guidelines stated in this policy.

#### Questions Or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us using this link: [customerservice@pureromance.com](mailto:customerservice@pureromance.com).

#### Security

Pureromance.com takes the following types of security measures to protect the information you provide to us: use of technologies and policies such as limited access data-centers, firewall technology, secure socket layer certificate authentication and limitations of administrative access to our systems. In addition, it is our policy not to send your credit card number via e-mail. In fact, this is a practice we encourage you to adopt in all of your Internet activities.

We have designed Pureromance.com to accept orders only from Web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology; for example, 4.0 versions or higher of Netscape Navigator, versions 5.01 or higher of Internet Explorer, versions 0.8 or higher of Firefox and versions 1.2 or higher of Safari.

While we implement the above security measures on this Site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible. Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online--for example on message boards, through e-mail or in chat areas--that information can be collected and used by others. No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

#### How You Can Update, Correct or Delete Your Information

You can access the information that we collect online and maintain through normal updating methods. To update, correct or delete this information, you can email [customerservice@pureromance.com](mailto:customerservice@pureromance.com) or call 866-ROMANCE.

During the normal course of doing business, we may to share your information among our business units, our affiliates and unaffiliated third parties as necessary in order to service orders you place with us.

#### **Third Party Practices**

The Privacy Policy of an advertiser or promotional service appearing at our site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read that policy before responding to the offer.
